之前跟你约会的那女的怎么样了
What's going on with that woman you're dating?
-我甩了她  -为什么
-I broke up with her.  -Why?
因为她说她再也不想见到我  我觉得这话太侮辱人了
She said she didn't want to see me anymore and I found that insulting.
我还以为你们发展不错呢  怎么了
I thought things were going well. What happened?
我也不知道  她甚至没告诉我原因
I don't know, she didn't even give me a reason.
小事一桩  我们可以一起推算
Oh, not a problem, we can figure this out.
女人拒绝拉杰的原因有哪些呢
What are the reasons women reject Raj?
求不玩这个游戏
Can we not play this game?
不爱玩游戏  这就算一个
Doesn't like games. That's one.
-别理他  -分手了你也别太难过
-Ignore him.  -Yeah, sorry about the breakup.
没关系  我没事
That's okay, I'm fine.
你当然没事啦
Of course you're fine.
一个物种里  本就不是全部都能找到伴
Not every member of a species finds a mate.
艾萨克·牛顿爵士到死都还是处男  你看看他对人类的贡献有多大
Sir Isaac Newton died a virgin. Look at the contributions he made.
谢尔顿  我不是处男
I'm not a virgin, Sheldon.
怎么  你觉得自己比艾萨克·牛顿还牛逼了吗
Wha... So now you think you're better than Isaac Newton?
难怪女人都不喜欢你
No wonder women don't like you.
你这样太损了
You're not being very nice.
哪有  他自己说他没事
What? He said he was fine.
有时人们所言非所想
Sometimes people say things they don't mean.
这是个悖论
Oh, that's a paradox.
如果你刚才的所言即所想
I-If you meant what you just said,
那就意味着你刚才所言可能非所想
then that means you may not have meant what you just said.
小心点  我在《星际迷航》看过这幕  很快他耳朵要冒出蒸汽了
Careful, I saw this on Star Trek. Smoke's gonna come out of his ears soon.
小伙子们  你们好吗
Hey, boys. How's it going?
我本以为我们大家在愉悦地交流
Well, I thought we were having a nice conversation,
结果发现  原来我是在冒犯人
but it turns out, I was being offensive.
-一如既往  -对...
- So, normal. - Yeah--
谢尔顿  你又干嘛了
Sheldon, what did you do?
我们在讨论拉杰最近分手的事  貌似是我没顾虑到他心情
We were discussing Raj's recent breakup and apparently, I was insensitive to him.
没关系  我没事
It's okay, I'm fine.
你有事  别中了他的计
You di-- Don't fall for it.
他会引诱你把他跟死去的处男做对比
He'll get you to compare him to a dead virgin,
然后突然间你就成了坏人
and suddenly you're the bad guy.
谢尔顿  我说我没事时
Sheldon, when I said I was fine,
我的意思是我不想再谈这件事了
I meant I didn't want to talk about it anymore.
那你为什么不直接这么说
Then why didn't you say that?
因为大家都不这么说
Because that's not what people do.
我宁愿大家直接告诉我他们心中真实的想法
Well, I would prefer if people told me exactly what is on their mind.
不  不会  你不会  你不会想要  我再强调几百遍都不够
No. No, you don't, you really don't.I actually can't say "Don't" enough.
这至少会让相处简单很多啊
Well, it certainly would be easier.
你们压根就不会懂
You have no idea what it's like
读不懂别人情绪的复杂心情
to struggle with recognizing emotional cues.
-想必是非常烦心吧  -是的  谢谢
-I'm sure it's extremely frustrating.  - Thank you.
还有点小伤心吧
And also a little sad.
够了  你现在就是在显摆你会读
O-Okay, now you're just showing off.
我读到麻省理工有个团队
You know, I just read that a team at MIT
制造出了一种可协助解读人类情绪的装置
developed a device that helps people read human emotions.
你觉得我们能让他们把谢尔顿重新编程吗  酷啊
And you think we can get those guys to reprogram Sheldon? Cool.
该装置的准确率好像能到85%呢
It's supposed to be accurate, like, 85% of the time.
我觉得有点难以置信
Wow, I find that hard to believe.
你不敢相信一群害羞内向
That a bunch of awkward scientists
零社交技能的科学家会发明这种机器来帮助他们读懂他人情绪吗
with no social skills would invent a machine to do it for them?
我收回我的话  我相信
I take it back. I believe it.
如果麻省理工有的话  我可以打电话问问啊
You know, if it's at MIT, I can make some calls.
或许可以帮谢尔顿搞个原型机来
Maybe we can get Sheldon a prototype.
你觉得如何
What do you think?
能读懂情绪的机器的确挺吸引人
A machine that reads emotions is intriguing.
它能帮我成为一个更体贴的朋友
It could help me be a more considerate friend.
那何尝不是件好事
Wouldn't that be nice.
还可以帮助我找出我的敌人  发现他们的恐惧  然后...
It could also help me identify my enemies,discover their fears and then...
我就能利用他们的恐惧来摧毁他们
I could use those fears to destroy them.
我喜欢第一种用法
I like the first one.
第十季  第十四集
现在谢尔顿搬到对面住了
Now that Sheldon's across the hall,
你决定好了要把他房间拿来干嘛吗
have you decided what you're doing with his old room?
我在想看是改成小藏书室或是游戏房
I was thinking maybe a library or a gaming room.
也可以改成火车玩具房啊
You could make it a train room.
我不喜欢火车  喜欢火车的是你
I don't like trains. You like trains.
我知道  可是艾米不让我弄个火车玩具房
I know, and Amy says I can't have a train room.
谢尔顿  麻省理工的人回复我了那个情绪解读机
Sheldon, I just heard from the guys at MIT about that emotion reader
他们会送个原型机过来  让你做发行前测试
They're sending a prototype for you to beta test.
太好了
Wonderful.
虽然我也不知道对成为实验小白鼠该作何感想
Although I'm not sure how I feel about being used as a guinea pig.
等你拿到机器  你就知道该作何感想啦
Well, when you get the machine, you can find out.
或许我可以拿来看看为什么女人不停甩我
Maybe I could use it to understand why women keep dumping me.
你不需要用机器啊
Oh, you don't need a machine for that,
你就发意见调查表给你所有的前女友
just send a survey card to all your ex-girlfriends
再告诉她们  填表的人有机会中奖就行了
and tell them if they fill it out they might win a prize.
这主意还不赖啊
That's actually not a bad idea.
或许我可以让她们齐聚一堂  弄成像...
Maybe I could even get them all together,sort of like a...
焦点小组  来探讨出我到底是哪里有问题
a focus group, to find out what's wrong with me.
别啊  拉杰  这是个馊主意
No, Raj, that's a terrible idea.
对啊  我刚才在瞎说
Yeah, I was joking.
你们...  真的吗
You... Really?
小秘诀  笑话结尾通常用
Uh, little tip: jokes are often better
"哇咔哇咔"或者是"哈恰恰"比较好
when you end them with "Wocka Wocka" or "Ha-cha-cha."
分别是电视节目《大青蛙布偶秀》中角色
与知名美国单口相声演员吉米·杜兰特的招牌语
好消息  我想买的大电视放得进游戏房
Hey, great news. The TV I want will fit in the gaming room,
而且如果我不拉上窗帘  我能从上班的地方看到
and if I leave the curtains open, I can watch it from work.
你能缓一缓改装那房间的事吗
Hey, can you hold off redoing the room?
我哥过几周会来这里
My brother's coming out here in a few weeks.
行啊  没问题  你哥哥怎么了
Oh. Yeah. Okay, sure. What's going on with your brother?
我爸让我帮忙把他弄进我们公司面试
My dad asked if I can get him a job interview at my work.
你确定这是个好主意吗
Is that a good idea?
你觉得他们会愿意让坐过牢的人去卖药丸吗
I mean, you think they'll consider someone who was in prison for selling drugs?
我卖的是药品
Well, I sell pharmaceuticals.
可以算是药丸的高档版了
That's just a really hard to spell word for drugs.
我相信他也会很庆幸以后工作
Well, I'm sure he'll appreciate
"药"的样品能用公事包装  而不是塞菊花里
carrying his samples in a briefcase instead of his colon.
你觉得他会住多久呢
How long do you think he'll stay?
不确定啊  可能几天吧  除非他面试过了  那我就说不准了
I-I'm not sure. Maybe a few days.Unless he gets the job, then who knows?
"说不准"  真让人激动啊
"Who knows?" That's exciting.
我可以每天早上醒来  看他是否还在
I'll get to wake up every morning and see if he's still here.
你不会是有意见吧
You don't have a problem with this, do you?
当然没有  他是你哥嘛
Of course not. I mean, he's your brother.
谢谢  你最好了
Okay. Thank you, you're the best.
新电视从墙上掉下来砸死我们时  记住这点
Remember that when the new TV falls off the wall and crushes us both.
这东西真酷
This thing's pretty cool.
利用无线信号
It interprets emotions using a wireless signal
分析呼吸和心率的细微变化来解读情绪
to analyze subtle changes in breathing and heart rate.
-机器可以做到这点  太厉害了  -是的
-It's amazing a machine can do that.  -Yes.
以后机器人叛变
Now, when the robots rise up,
他们会知道一直以来我都是支持他们的
they'll know that I've been rooting for them the whole time.
显示器和你的手机同步了
The display is synced to your phone.
-来试试  -好的
-Give it a try.  -All right.
我会看一些照片激发情绪反应
Now, I'm gonna look at some pictures to prompt an emotional response,
我们来看看  这台机器能否准确识别
and we'll see if the machine can identify them accurately.
记住  它只能检测到开心  伤心  生气和激动
Okay, remember, it can only detect happy, sad,angry and excited.
不是其他那种复杂感觉  比如 "我是作什么死啊"
Not other things you're feeling, like,"What have I done with my life?"
好的  我在看第一张照片
Okay, I'm looking at the first picture.
你开心吗？
You are...happy?
我在看小狗
Yes. I'm looking at puppies.
有人无视了它们小小尖尖的牙齿  不过算了
Somebody's ignoring their tiny needle teeth,but all right.
-换一张  -好的
- Try another one. - Okay.
它说我的感觉是什么
What does it say I'm feeling?
-伤心  -是的
-Sad.  -Yes.
我在看我奶奶的照片
I'm looking at a picture of my grandma.
这就对了  因为她去世了  你想念她
Oh, that makes sense, 'cause she's gone and you miss her.
是的
Yes.
你担心以后颈部也会像她那样松弛
And you're worried that turkey neck is in your future.
现在它说你很生气  别转换得这么快行吗
What, now, see... now it says you're mad.Make up your mind.
好的  艾米丽  很好  到时见
Okay, Emily. Yeah, sounds great. See you then.
是你的前女友艾米丽吗
Is that Emily your ex-girlfriend?
是的  我请所有前女友齐聚一堂讨论
Yeah. I'm getting all my exes together in order to discuss
她们为什么和我分手  我怎么能成为一名更棒的男友
why they broke up with me and how I can be a better boyfriend.
老天  你真这么做啦  你什么毛病啊
Oh, God. You went through with that? What is wrong with you?
我们将寻找出答案
We are going to find out.
你为什么要这么做  拉杰
Why would you do that, Raj?
我希望得到令我改进的信息
Well, I want information in order to improve myself.
你不会得到信息
You're not gonna get information,
你只会得到伤害你感情的批评
you're just gonna get criticism that hurts your feelings.
别担心  我是个大男人  我脸皮很厚的
Don't worry, I'm a grown man. I have a thick skin.
-真是个白痴  -干嘛啦
-You're so stupid.  -Hey!
你看下我哥的简历好吗
Hey, would you take a look at my brother's résumé?
我在帮他写得漂亮一点
I'm trying to help him clean it up a little.
好的
Yeah, sure.
他真的和缉毒署合作过吗
He really worked with the Drug Enforcement Agency?
他在戴上手铐前不知道  那也算
He didn't know it till he was cuffed, but yeah.
莱纳德  如果你开心你会知道
Hey, Leonard, if you're happy and you know it,
不需要拍手[儿歌]  因为我有情绪解读机
no need to clap your hands,because I have an emotion detector.
-用着怎么样  -出奇好
-How's it working out?  -Surprisingly well.
真好  我为你开心
That's great, I'm happy for you.
等等
No, wait, uh, hold on.
你是真开心啊  真是好人
Oh, what, you are. Aren't you sweet?
这是什么  你在写简历吗
What's that? Are you working on your resume?
不  是我哥的  我想帮他在这里找工作
No, it's my brother's. I'm trying to help him get a job out here.
这令莱纳德生气了
And that makes Leonard angry.
没有
No, it doesn't.
拜托  莱纳德  生气的表情我还是认识的
What, Leonard, please. I know an angry face when I see it.
手机上这个红色皱眉的家伙代表生气
It's this red frowny guy on my phone.
怎么  我哥要来你很生气吗
What? Are you really upset about Randall coming?
-没有  -有
- No. - Yes.
-我说了没有  -它和你的表情完全一样好吗
- I said no. - I-It's like you're twins.
莱纳德  如果你生气  直接告诉我
Leonard, if you're mad about this, just tell me.
好吧  你邀请你的毒贩哥哥来和我们一起住  天知道住多长时间
Fine. You invited your drug dealer brother to stay with us for God knows how long
却事先根本没问过我
and didn't bother to ask me first.
他是我哥  我不觉得我需要你的允许
He's my brother! I didn't think I needed your permission.
瞧  现在她也生气了
Well, hey. Now she's angry, too.
这东西太牛逼了
This thing works like gangbusters.
我不是说你必须得到我的允许
I'm not saying you have to ask my permission,
但你在答应前  好歹知会我一声吧
but you could have talked to me about it before you said it was okay.
像你知会我  你的游戏室那样吗
Like you talked to me about your gaming room?
我们的游戏室  我还打算往里摆一个香薰蜡烛呢
Our gaming room! I was gonna put a scented candle in it.
他还在生气
He's still mad.
别幸灾乐祸
Stop enjoying their fight.
你好意思说我
You first.
如果你这么不高兴  我告诉你时  你为什么不说
you were this upset,why didn't you say so when I told you?
因为我不想表现得像混蛋一样
Because I didn't want to sound like a jerk.
你现在就是个混蛋
Well, you sound like one now.
我不觉得我哥来住一段时间有什么大不了的
I don't see the big deal if my brother comes and stays for a while.
如果你帮他找到工作  他会永远住在这里
If you get him a job, he's gonna live here forever!
他会自己找住处
He would get his own place.
-他这辈子有过自己的住处吗  -有过
-Has he ever had his own place?  -Yes!
床边就是金属马桶吗[牢房]
Did it have a metal toilet next to the bed?
那...也算啊
It still counts.
这和你逼我与谢尔顿一起住 有什么区别
You know, how is this any different from you making me live with Sheldon?
你...太伤人了  人家的蜂蜜坚果脆谷乐都跟你分享了
You... Hey! I shared my Honey Nut Cheerios with you.
你每个月底都给我账单好嘛
You gave me a bill at the end of every month.
别在这里瞎掺和
Stay out of this.
这事就是你和你那台烂机器挑起来的
You and your stupid machine started this fight!
你该庆幸这台情感机器不具备任何情感
You are lucky that this feelings machine doesn't have feelings.
-好了  谢尔顿  咱们走吧  -乐意至极
-Come on, Sheldon, let's go.  -Gladly.
我们可以摔门而去吗
Can we storm out?
你说出来就失去了震撼效果了
I think it loses its impact if we're chatting about it.
好吧  那我就对他们比那根手指吧
Fine. I'll just give them the finger.
好了  首先  感谢各位大驾光临
Okay, first off,I want to thank you all so much for coming.
霍华德将为艾米丽担任手语翻译 同时负责记笔记
Howard is here to interpret for Emily,and to take notes.
初登场第5季第4集  是聋哑人士
不  他不觉得这样做很傻逼
No, he doesn't think it's stupid.
先说一下  由于你们俩都叫艾米丽
Uh, heads up, both of you are named Emily,
所以我们称你为"红发艾米丽"
so we'll call you "Red-headed Emily"
初登场第7集第17集
而你是"红发艾米丽2号"
and you, "Red-headed Emily, Junior."
初登场在第5季第4集
当初和他交往的人是你不是我
Hey, you went out with him. I didn't.
好了  我们开始吧
Okay, uh, let's get things started.
我们先轮流来
Um, why don't we go around the room,
介绍你的名字  以及和我分手的原因
say your name,and why you broke up with me.
你想先开始吗
Want to kick it off?
好的
Oh, okay. Um...
初登场在第5季第4集
我叫露西  我和拉杰分手是因为  我患有严重的社会焦虑症
I'm Lucy,and I broke up with Raj because I have severe social anxiety,
而他总是强行将我置于非常尴尬的境地
and he kept trying to force me into uncomfortable situations.
比如现在这样吗
Like this one?
没错
Yeah.
的确如此  我有时对别人的底线不太敏感
I did do that.I can be insensitive to other people's boundaries.
霍华德  你能帮我记下来吗
Howard, would you write that down?
脑子进水   记好了
Oh... schmuck. Got it.
下一位
Uh, next?
好的
Okay. Um...
我叫克莱尔
I'm Claire.
初登场第9季第14集
我想我和你分手的原因  主要是你太黏人了
And I guess I broke up with you because you were just really needy.
而且你还非常虚荣
Also, you were incredibly vain--
比如你花了好多时间修你的眉型...
like, all the time you spent shaping your eyebrows...
新规则  每个人只能说一条
Okay, new rule-- everybody only gets one.
下一个
Uh, next?
我不知道自己能不能
Ooh, I'm not sure I'm comfortable
在霍华德面前说出我们交往的细节
sharing details about our relationship in front of Howard.
他是来支持我的
He's here to support me,
你什么都可以在他面前说
so anything you have to say you can say in front of him.
好吧  每次我俩上床时...
Okay. Well, whenever you and I were in bed...
霍华德  滚出去
Howard, get out.
门都没有
Not a chance.
刚才你说到拉杰床上功夫相当烂
So, you were telling us how Raj was terrible in bed.
谢尔顿  晚饭做好了
Sheldon, dinner's ready.
我做了牛肉糜卷
I made beef loaf,
因为我知道你不喜欢菜名含糊的肉糜卷
because I know you're uncomfortable with the non-specificity of meat loaf.
谢尔顿
Sheldon?
-你没事吧  -人家很不好
-Hey, are you okay?  -Not really.
你怎么了
What's going on?
我真希望自己没用过那机器
I wish I never tried that device.
我知道上次用过按摩椅后  我也说了同样的话
And I know I said the same thing after the massage chair,
但这次我是认真的
but this time I mean it.
我很抱歉莱纳德和佩妮伤害了你的感情
I'm sorry Leonard and Penny hurt your feelings.
比那个严重多了  是我的问题
It's more than that. It's me.
我一直都知道  自己在解读别人情绪方面有困难
I always knew I had trouble recognizing other people's emotions,
但机器把这个问题凸显了出来
but that machine just made it so real.
每个人都有需要帮助的问题
Well, everybody has things that they need help with.
比如我  我摘了眼镜就看不清楚
Like me-- I can't see without my glasses.
现在我看你就是一个
And right now you're just a,
可爱的粉团子 裹着一身孩子气的绿团子
a cute, pink smudge wearing a childish green smudge.
我以为自己有进步了  结果并没有
I thought I was getting better at it, but clearly I'm not.
你改善很多了
Yes, you are.
好几次我不开心时  你都看出来了
There have definitely been days when I was sad and you could tell.
但那就像是瓮中捉鳖  手到擒来
Yeah, but that's shooting fish in a barrel.
你本身就是个悲伤聚合体
You're kind of a sad sack.
抱歉  我不该怎么说  我只是很难过
I'm sorry, I shouldn't have said that.I'm just upset.
不  你看
No, see, right there,
你能觉察到你伤了我的心
you knew you hurt my feelings.
我真为你骄傲  这肯定是受了我爸影响
And I'm proud of you for reasons I'm sure have something to do with my father.
如果你不喜欢那台机器  就不要用了
And if you don't like that machine, get rid of it.
因为我爱的就是原来的你
Because I love you exactly the way you are.
我对你也是这种感觉
I feel the same way about you.
现在把你的眼镜带上  你看起来怪怪的
Now, put your glasses back on. You look weird.
我觉得你很好  但是  我的妈呀
I thought you were great,but, oh, my God,
你被你父母控制得太多了
you were so dominated by your parents.
没错  这点经常让我抓狂  他这人有点妈宝男
Oh, yeah, and that used to drive me nuts. He's kind of a mama's boy.
-岂止有一点  -好了 够了
- Kind of? - Whoa, okay! That's enough.
你就写"惹人爱的好儿子"
Write down "Loving son."
我可以说两句吗
Can I just say something?
和拉杰交往
Going out with Raj
是我遇到的最幸运的事
was one of the best things that ever happened to me.
很好  我愿意和你复合
Yes, I'll take you back.
让我说完
Let me finish.
感觉就像因为跟他交往了之后
It's like I needed to go through that experience
我才知道我不想要什么样的男人
to know what exactly I don't want in a man.
这话真伤人  不过我还是愿意和你复合
Well, that's hard to hear, but I'll still take you back.
我也有这种感觉
You know, the same thing happened to me.
我和拉杰分手后  我遇到了盖瑞  他简直太棒了
After I broke up with Raj, I met Gary,who's just amazing.
打扰下  拼写是一个R还是两个
Sorry, is that "Gary" with one R or two?
别写了好吗
Would you stop writing?!
慢着  你们所有人在和我分手后  都有了更美好的恋情吗
Just wait. So... did all of you go on to better relationships after me?
-是的  -毫无疑问
-Oh, yeah.  -Without question.
我是在分手前就有了
Little before, actually.
你可得牢牢抓住他
Don't let him get away.
慢着  她说什么
Wait. What did she say?
可以这样说  甩了你 换来个蝙蝠侠
Uh, basically, she traded you for Bruce Wayne.
我们还是到此结束吧
Okay, maybe we should just end this.
慢着
Wait, hang on.
我想为在座各位指出
I just want to point out to everyone here,
这个男人竭尽全力想让自己更优秀
this is a man who is going to great lengths to better himself.
甚至冒着被羞辱的风险  至少我觉得这样做很勇敢
Even at the risk of...being humiliated. And I, for one, think that's very brave.
谢谢你  霍华德
Thank you, Howard.
说实话  我很意外你俩没有开花结果
Honestly, I'm surprised you two didn't wind up together.
和你们一样
Well, like you gals,
我得先经历他这场风雨 才能找到我老婆这道彩虹
I had to suffer through him to find Bernadette.
-什么事  -我们应该向你道歉
-Yes?  -We owe you an apology.
没事啦  你需要手提箱  我不在家  你就借走个手提箱嘛
Oh, it's fine. You needed a suitcase,I wasn't home, you borrowed a suitcase.
那是六年前的事了  我说的是今晚
That was six years ago. I'm talking about tonight.
我以为按时间先后顺序来道歉
Well, I thought we were going in order.
我俩之间刚好世界大战爆发
Look, we got really angry at each other,
而你正好撞上了
and you just got caught in the middle of it.
还有  手提箱的事很抱歉
And...sorry about the suitcase.
道歉是应该的
Yeah, well, you should be.
里面还有你的袜子 我只能扔了
Your socks were still in it.I had to throw it away.
总之  我相信你们已经解决了矛盾
Anyway,I, uh, trust that you've resolved your conflict.
-是  我们没事了  -佩妮会打电话给她爸爸说
-Yes, we're fine.  -Mm, Penny's gonna call her dad and tell him
他哥现在来时机不太好
it's not a good time for Randall to visit.
只希望他不会生气
Hopefully, he won't be too upset.
你是他的小棉袄  他哪能气你多久
Oh, you're his little girl-- he can't stay mad at you.
他当然不会生我的气
He won't be mad at me.
是你不想让我哥来  所以...
I mean, you're the one who doesn't want my brother to come, so...
所以你想让我背黑锅吗
So you're gonna throw me under the bus?
我会让你背个大大的黑锅  那锅大到可以给全村做饭了
Oh, I'm gonna throw you so hard,I might actually win a stuffed animal.
两位  听起来你们又生气了
Uh, guys, it sounds like you're getting angry again.
-那是因为这是事实  -太好了
-That's because we are.  -Yes!
我不需要情绪解读机  我就是情绪解读机
I don't need an emotion machine! I am one!
多谢了  女士们  太有意思了
Thanks, ladies! This was fun!
下次的诡异尴尬夜  别让我们期待太久哦
Let's not wait so long for another bizarre, awkward night.
真是浪费时间  我真是白痴
Well, that was a waste of time.I'm such an idiot.
别这么自责  批评你是我的工作
Don't beat yourself up. That's what I'm here for.
也许我不该定下来  也许我要在花丛中过一过
Maybe I won't settle down.Maybe I'll just play the field.
花丛刚才就在这屋里  花丛拒绝了
Yeah, the field was just here. The field said no.
兄弟  别这样
Dude, come on.
这样吧  我们约好
Okay, I'll tell you what.I'll make you a deal.
三十年后  如何你依然单身
30 years from now, if you're still single
而我和伯纳黛特也离婚了
and things don't work out with me and Bernadette...
咱俩可以试试
you and I can give it a go.
感谢你的好意  但如果你俩离婚了
I appreciate the offer, but if things don't work out with you two,
我一定像秃鹰一样扑向她
I'm swooping in on her like a vulture.
太迟了  斯图尔特先订了
Too late. Stuart called dibs.
从理论上说
But theoretically,
如果我们是同志关系
if you and I were in a gay relationship,
我们怎么告诉大家  贴出公告吗
how would we tell people? Like, print up announcements?
我不知道  贴了公告会有区别吗
I don't know. What difference does it make?
我希望所有同志游行都能邀请我们
Well, I want to make sure we get invited to all the parades.
听起来的确有趣
Those do look fun.
是啊
Yeah.
如果你想穿网眼露脐装去游行 你最好别碰蘸酱
Well, if you want to march in a fishnet crop top,you better lay off that dip.
如果你不想让我吃  为什么摆出来
If you didn't want me to eat it,why'd you put it out?
是给姑娘们的  她们甩了我  我才不管她们是否会长胖
It was for the girls.They broke up with me-- I don't care if they get fat.
我不会长胖的
I'm not gonna get fat.
想打赌吗  你从来不锻炼
Oh, you want to bet? You never exercise.
瞧着  我现在就锻炼
Fine. Look, I'll exercise right now.
一
One...
二
two...
对了  这是仰卧起坐[很脆]
These are crunches, by the way.
真够成熟的  继续这样吃  你会发心脏病的
Very mature.Keep eating like that.You're gonna have a heart attack.
好的  我这样吃呢
Okay. How about if I eat like this?
你真幼稚
You're such a child.
对你未来老公  你就这种态度吗
Hey, is that any way to talk to your future husband?
我只是假设  我永远不会和你结婚的
Hey, I was being hypothetical, okay? I would never marry you.
得了  等你看到我选的求婚戒指时  你会感动到喷泪
Please. When you see the ring I pick out, you're gonna melt.
想得美
Yeah, right.
是玫瑰金的吗
Wait, is it rose gold?
别告诉我  我想有个惊喜
Actually, don't tell me. I want to be surprised.
你最后把机器送回去了吗
So, did you wind up sending that machine back?
是的  我都不确定它的准度到底行不行
I did. You know, I'm not even sure how accurate it was.
我把它拿到火车商店  它说所有人都很伤心[悲哀]
I took it to the train store-- it said everyone was sad.
我终于把哈雷哄睡着了
I finally got Halley to sleep.
我刚看到有一项研究说  初为人母的人
You know, I just read a study that suggests new mothers are better
-在情绪感知方面比普通人多两年优势  -这是真的
-at senseing emotions for up to two years.  -It's ture.
怀孕引起大脑的生理变化
Pregnancy causes physiological change in the brain,
导致感同身受的能力增加
and resulting increase empathetic.
原来我们只需要搞大谢尔顿的肚子就行
So all we need to do is got Shledon knocked up.
不行  我在动物收容所找到他时  他已经被阉了
We can't. He's already fixed when I found him at the shelter.
伯纳黛特  我们来测试下这一理论  你觉得我现在有什么感受
Hey, Bernadette, let's test this theory.What're you thinking I'm feeling right now?
来看看  你比我们优秀  有点可怜我们
Let's see.You're better than us? A little bit sorry for us?
但最主要是开心不必成为我们这样的人
But mostly gald you don't have to be us.
接着让她大肚子  她真厉害
Keep filling this one with baby, she's good.